[Music]
as october frost spreads over the valley
my home is transformed into shades of
red and gold
there's a distinct smell in the air
of pine trees and wet earth
i love it and while i had a very
different type of video planned out for
you this week
something unexpected happened and i
wanted to share it i don't really have a
reason to only that it has been a very
happy time
and it felt right to share a little
glimpse into our celebrations
i remember watching movies about love
stories when i was a child in most cases
the couples in them go through a
whirlwind romance of roller coaster
emotions fighting one day and making up
the next
it definitely made an exciting plot but
after several difficult relationships in
my adult life i realized that
at least for me
my experience of love would never be
like those stories
true love wasn't something that happened
at first glance
it surfaced over the course of years and
through countless acts of kindness and
commitment
a timeline that these movies didn't
always portray which would make the
story less exciting from the outside but
extremely meaningful nonetheless it was
an assurance that in my case love isn't
temporary but a more stable foundation
of trust
through negative experiences i've come
to value people who try their best to
approach situations with kind words and
patience instead of hurt and disrespect
choosing to cultivate a gentle energy
instead of chaos
being open to see themselves as
imperfect to communicate to listen
while everyone's definition of love
their personal experiences and beliefs
are different i'm happy i found someone
who shares mine
and we hope to enjoy a future of growing
in love together
[Music]
do
as you can see i have um
i went out into the garden and took the
very last of the flowers that are
holding on
that haven't succumbed to the autumn
frost yet and i decorated because it
just felt like appropriately celebratory
so yeah and of course i put on a nice
dress as well because it felt like the
best way to celebrate with you guys
one thing that my boyfriend and i do a
lot is that we
spend the weekends
going on hikes or doing things and i
usually bring my camera and that's kind
of one way we can
have some time together plus i get to
capture some amazing moments on the
hikes and all that to share with you
guys
luke was very sneaky about
the proposal because he convinced me to
walk up on this ledge where he could
film me and help me make my video and he
was it just seemed like he was really
trying to be very helpful but he um
ended up asking me to marry him there so
he was then through that able to capture
it on camera so that's really special
too he has made me quite a few very
beautiful wire wrapped rings but
the one he gave me as the engagement
ring is actually one that was passed
down to him
from his grandmother and it's over 60
years old it's very beautiful and i know
you really haven't seen luke that much
in the videos and that's mostly just
because i like to respect the privacy of
the people in my life for for obvious
reasons but i will definitely get them
on camera sometime soon anyway the
reason i'm also sharing this news is
because that means that
this channel will change
sometime next year i'm not sure quite
sure when
but
i won't be living in this little house
forever
and
fairly soon things will change and
i will no doubt share parts of that with
you but it's it's a big step for me
things will go on as normal and yet they
will be completely changed as well so
anyway i didn't really have a good
reason to share this only that i just
wanted to share some joy and share some
good news and
again thank all of you for all the
support and kindness you've shown me
luke also loves being part of the videos
and helping me make them and i have read
to him many of your comments especially
in the video
that i made with him in which i showed
his jewelry
and i will leave that video linked down
below if you want to see a little more
of him
anyway it has been a eventful autumn
already so stay tuned for more autumn
videos and i'm just very excited to
share little updates along the way it
was such an exciting thing that happened
i just didn't know what else to do but
to share so i noticed there was quite a
few new people here recently so please
feel free to comment down below and
introduce yourself
i really do enjoy reading the comments
and i know quite a few people comment
every video or almost every video
and so i i do notice that and i do
really value your continued support and
feedback so i'm sending you all my love
and i hope you have a wonderful day or
nights
goodbye
oh my god eiger
move
you're right there
you move anyway either way just back or
forth left or right buddy